Tokimeki Balmeter Rising TV
This is Ichibara.
A little while ago, I appeared in costume, said a few words, and then we posed together.
Kimiki Pose Rock-paper-scissors.
We are going to release our new album "Tokimeki Koe to Seishun" in the near future.
Thank you very much.
Well, you know, everyone has already seen the videos of the songs on YouTube, so I am sure you have seen them,
Today, we are going to talk about the charms of the new songs on the new album.
Thank you very much.
It's really good.
Oh, my God.
Spoilers? I heard it's not allowed, but...but...but..,
But this project itself is like a spoiler, isn't it? That's true.
But last time, they asked us to hide it in a good way if we spoiled anything.
Maybe it says something about bad intentions.
I'm the type of person who thinks it's okay to spoil things, so I'm on your side.
Yes, I'm on your side. I'm sure you're in that camp, too.
Let's go for it.
So, the first song is "Se-no,
Happy Lovable!
But you know, they were dancing on the radio.
What? In the video?
That's what he told me.
He did?
Yes, that's right. He said something about it.
Well, I'm sure they've released the music video or something. Well, I'm sure they've already released the music video or something.
I think everyone has already heard this one.
It was released on the radio I was listening to.
It was the lead song.
You're wearing the same outfit as in the music video.
Well, there are a lot of things.
Yes, yes, yes.
Don't you think it's a very nice word?
Happy, love, youth blue, hapira blue.
It's got it all written all over it.
Did you guys search for this song?
You know, before this song came out,
I wondered if the word "Hapila Blue" existed in the first place.
I did a search, and there were searches for everything.
Yes, yes.
That's right.
So, it was coined.
I thought, "Thank you so much already for making such a wonderful coined word.
Right.
Hapila Blue.
I want to end it.
Whenever I have a happy occasion, I say Hapila Blue.
Hapila blue.
Hey, it's nice.
Hapila blue. Uchirara, hapira blue.
Like, "Ujira, Hapira Blue.
Last time, the pause rock-paper-scissors game, you know.
Oh, that's right.
Yay.
Remember this? Spoiler? Some people wrote something like that.
Yes.
Spoilers are spoilers.
It's already been posted a lot. In many places.
Please do it, everyone.
Please do it.
It's up-tempo, and when you listen to it, you'll get into a really detailed mood.
You can get into the mood.
Let's move on to the next song, shall we?
Okay.
Okay, the next song.
Superlative,
Cute.
Go ahead.
Here you go.
It's kind of hard to hold still, isn't it?
I could never do that.
I dance. That's why I'm like this.
We're all like this. I'm on my back.
I'm going to hold my hands a little bit.
Yes, yes, yes. This is Pio. Yes, yes, yes. This is for Pio.
Yes, yes, yes. My favorite singer-songwriter
Mr. Korezawa wrote the lyrics for this song.
Thank you so much.
I'm so happy.
Even though it's a song about a lost love, it doesn't make me feel down.
She handled it in a positive way.
Aren't the lyrics really cute?
It's cute.
The endings, "I'm going to do it," "I'm going to cry," and everything.
Is that it? Is this a "show-stopper"?
I wonder how far I've come.
It's like that. It's a very cute song with cute endings, lyrics, and dance moves.
Aki-chan's first line
I can't say, but I like it.
Is it really the first song?
I like it.
I like it. I like it.
It's delicious.
The way Aki-chan sings is cute, isn't it?
It's cute.
The lyrics of this song.
Really?
It fits perfectly.
That part where she sings by herself is cute, too.
What? What?
Where?
In front of one, like, one.
Oh, before the one.
But before that, Julia's cute little girl is coming, too.
Ah...
There's a lot of "cute".
Indeed. Indeed.
It's a different word from the usual "cute.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Listen to this. Everyone.
Listen to this.
Enjoy.
Next song, Se-no.
The Days You Spend
Okay, please.
Have you noticed?
I've been wanting to.
Right now,
Just,
I'll start with you.
Just a feeling.
Fall in love.
Yeah! Yay!
You endured, Hiyori-chan.
Hiyori, you endured.
I thought you were an athlete, so sweaty from recording.
It's really true.
It was like someone's room was physically noticed.
Yes, yes, yes.
That kind of thing?
I was the first one to go cold.
I was the second, recording.
I was cold, so I built a heater.
Heating?
Heating. And it was 28 degrees.
Is that what you mean?
It was that hot?
Yes, it was. I went to bed and turned the temperature up, thinking it wasn't getting warm enough,
I forgot to turn it off.
Then the next person and the next person after that felt it was too hot.
It was like being in a sauna.
I didn't feel that bad.
I was getting more and more excited singing to myself,
So, with everything going on, I was in a sauna?
Yes, I was.
I didn't feel that bad.
I'm so sorry. I'm that sorry.
I have to take a water bath.
It must be cold.
This song takes a lot of energy. Even singing it.
That one?
I like the end. The sausage.
But dancing is good, too.
We all do it together.
We all do it together,
We can make eye contact.
That's right.
Communication is different.
I think that's a point of interest. I think so.
You seem to like Mr. V like that.
I think so.
Also, the way Oharu sings is cool.
It's cool. And just now, too.
Yay.
It was really flowing.
It's good, listen to it.
I'm also jinning, jinning.
Enjoy it.
Well then, the next song is super cute,
It's a song with a lot of love in it.
Seino.
I love it so much. I love it.
I am.
I, well, Pretty girl, Min-chan is кас byte.
Go!
Ah!
Japanese.
Kosugi-san still can't get any place for such a yay performance.
Dai Oyaman draw him the first 23E NEW TONIGHT
Please do.
Thank you very much.
me
Ah!
It's a heart, right?
It's normal. I just felt like giving a heart.
I did.
I made it small, but I remember.
Spoiler limit.
Limit?
I'm over the limit.
Over the limit.
It's cute, isn't it, Miriritsukeshite.
Miriritsukeshite.
It's so cute.
I like the fact that you are teaching different levels of skills to each one of them.
The last part, the folding in. Last, in the fold.
That's good.
If you call out "I love you" and "I love you" all over the venue, and you do mag-age to everyone.
I want you to say I love you.
I love you.
I think I'd like to do something like that.
But you know, the lyrics are sweet and lovely.
But the choruses are powerful, and it's like the song is really filled with feelings,
It's like the song is really filled with feelings.
The song is like that, and I think it will be a lot of fun at the live performance.
Let's all go beyond our limits.
Yes, let's go beyond the limit.
Let's go beyond the limits.
But, you know, who am I singing with?
You know, what's the problem?
You know, we all feel like we've grown very young.
That's why,
Aki-chan, you're about 3 years old.
You're about that age, too.
Really?
Oh, you are about 5 years old.
Ah, a 2 year old.
Two years old.
A little older, a little older.
I thought I'd be able to see everyone as a baby. I think you'll see a lot of baby people.
It's an honest reminder.
And it's a bit like a line, isn't it?
I had never seen a line like this before.
It's like, "Oh, no, I don't want to be too cute.
Julian there was a bit like a musical actress,
I like it.
Oh.
She sings, you know, she sings in a kind of cute way, you know,
I think the way she sings in this album is different from the others.
Doesn't your voice sound different?
Yes, I do.
I can understand that.
But there was one more thing that sounded like Julian's musical voice,
Me.
Ahhh....
I feel like I'm singing in a strange country, like in a cartoon.
It's different from usual.
It's like, "What is it?
That part is good, too.
Is it in the middle?
I think it's right in the middle. Right in the middle.
The middle?
That's where I sing the most.
I sing in a completely different way, so that might be a little bit interesting. The way they sing is totally different, so that might be kind of interesting too.
Please check it out.
Next up?
This song focuses on JULIA's part.
Se-no, my dream won't stop.
Reitoku Ukisho
Let's run through love.
It's nice, isn't it?
It's exactly the kind of song whose lyrics are exactly what we are thinking right now, isn't it?
Yes. Yes. Yes, it is.
It's fun.
Isn't it fun to dance?
The choreography is very youthful.
I really like the last part, and I want to choreograph it at the end.
The pause at the end is really nice, too.
I understand.
But you have to get it right at the end.
Yes, that's right.
It's a little bit too "shun," so we want to make sure we get it right.
We can't get enough of our dreams, can we?
You have captured all of that in your song, so I'm sure you'll be able to sing along.
The song is a little bright, but I feel like I can sing it at a live performance.
That's for sure.
It's amazing. The lyrics are passionate.
It makes you look forward to your dreams. And this song? It's something to look forward to dream about, isn't it? And then there's this song.
What?
I'm going to dance and think I'm not supposed to talk.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
This song makes me think that even though I've reached my goal, my dreams will continue to grow even more from now on.
It makes me feel super positive. It's a song that makes you feel confident.
Yeah, yeah.
I really want to listen to it before a live performance.
Yeah, it's true. For sure.
Please listen to it.
Yes.
Then, please listen to the next song.
Seino.
Lami-Lami-Lami.
Lamarami.
Llami llami.
Llami llami. Lami lami.
Lami lami.
No, this one.
Are you sure?
No, really, it's like our trophy.
It worked.
I mean, look at it. It's a funny song.
You might think it's a funny song, but it's really cool.
It's really cool.
I like it a lot.
It's a little sexy.
Sexy.
The dance in the chorus is sexy.
But I can't do it at all.
You did it so well the other day.
You're getting good at it.
We're all in sync.
This is it, isn't it?
That was too much fun.
We couldn't get certain parts of the choreography to line up.
Everyone was doing it in a different way.
It was like one DJ.
Two DJs.
I have a favorite part.
I can't tell you yet, but..., I may not be able to tell you yet,
Hiyori's part in the chorus is really good.
Hiyori's part is really good,
It was really cool or something like that, but then suddenly,
Suddenly,
She became like a cute and fragile girl,
That's what makes it so cute,
It feels good.
I'll try my best.
We were so sexy when we were dancing there.
Very sexy.
That was so bad. That was bad.
That was bad.
That was the sexiest thing I've ever seen,
Because she was singing,
I was afraid that everyone would focus on that,
Everyone was singing "foo, foo, foo, foo,
It's a song where you can feel all the sexiness of the people,
You can feel the sexiness of the people in this song.
It's like, everyone's eyes are drawn to it.
What do you think? Which do you want to pull out of the live camera?
The one where I'm singing?
What are you going to do? What are you going to do?
Oh, my God, that's not good.
Show me. Show me.
Okay, Hiyori, let's go next to her. Okay, Hiyori, let's go next door.
Oh, don't go next to me.
Hiyori, you can put this inside of me.
Is this okay? Shall we do that?
I hope you're looking forward to the show.
Last one.
Seino,
Iran Grab!
Iran grab!
Irangrab!
I don't know, I guess it's a moment song in this album, just in case.
A moment song.
I like the choreography.
Really.
I want you to see it in the big picture.
I like the members singing the choreography of the chorus.
I understand.
The singing voice is new, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I like that part of the chorus.
I like that part.
It's in the lyrics, and I love that one.
Try to grab it sometime.
Please do.
You sound fruitless.
But it's kind of a heartbreak song, like every now and then, but I think if you listen to it, you'll understand, But it's a bit of a heartbreak song, like the ones I've done in the past, but I think you'll understand if you listen to it,
It's also a little different, a little more mature, or so I thought,
Certainly a little mature.
But I guess there's a deep wound in his heart from the betrayal,
I can feel it right away when I listen to this song.
You can feel it immediately when you listen to this song.
I saw the special site for the album. Then, I saw the comments from the people who made the album,
I saw it.
I referred to the part where it says, "Yuragurabu, I was changed without being declared, and I didn't want that to happen.
I was not happy about it.
It's amazing.
I thought, "It's going to end.
I especially referred to Koizumi-san's reference to that.
No, since then.
Then you can write lyrics like that.
I'm sure of it.
I thought it was amazing.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for writing them like that.
So, these are the seven new songs on the album.
As the theme of the album is "love and youth," there are many songs that are divided into love and youth,
I think it is an album that can make you feel various kinds of feelings.
I wonder which songs will be performed where and when.
Will we be able to hear them?
If I don't come to both, maybe I won't be able to hear them all. If you don't come to both, maybe you won't hear the whole story.
But I hope you'll listen.
We're splitting up, aren't we?
That's right. Love and youth are separated.
If you want to hear the whole story, I'll be waiting for you both days.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'll be waiting for you. It's a wonderful album. Please listen to it a lot.
Please listen to it.
I'm going to listen to it.
lab
Someone must be crying somewhere.
Just a little bit of my feelings
I want to share it with you
I still don't know the landscape in front of me
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart
Paint a piece of the future
And it's guiding me
I'll do it now
Whenever you're lost, remember the reason for your tears
And when it's raining, I'll smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, puddles of sound
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a flower, my tears are making me dance
I'll wear a rainbow dress
Subtitle: Kiyo Hiyo
Please subscribe to our channel!